Guide to the Conklin and Rossant Reston project collection, 1960-1990
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Conklin and Rossant Reston project collection
1960-1990
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Conklin and Rossant
C0161
12.75 linear feet (26 boxes)
The Conklin and Rossant Reston project collection is divided into six series with four subseries. The collection includes items that relate to the construction and planning of Reston by Conklin and Rossant Architects. The collection begins with the initial plans done by Rossant before he and Conklin formed their architectural firm in 1967. The documents include plans, reports, correspondence and brochures about Reston. Also included are photographs, drawings and negatives which were used in the construction of Reston.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by William Conklin and James Rossant on June 24, 1991.
Historical Information
James S. Rossant designed the new town of Reston, Virginia, and completed the master plan for Reston in 1963. Rossant also designed the First Village Center in Reston which opened in 1966. The master plan pioneered and introduced many innovative planning ideas, including the new town around seven village centers and a town center. Then in 1967, Rossant joined with William Conklin to form Conklin and Rossant Architects and continued working on Reston. The partnership lasted until 1995. Following that William Conklin joined with Michael Costantin to form Conklin Costantin Architects. James Rossant has since become the president of James Rossant Architects which was created in 1995. Rossant has recently acted as a consultant to Lake Anne Village and has guided the renovation of some of its buildings and sculpture.
William J. Conklin was born on May 2, 1923 in Hebron, Nebraska. He studied architecture at Harvard University, graduating in 1950 with a M.Arch. Shortly following his graduation, he began work at the IBEC Corporation in New York City. By 1951, however, Conklin left IBEC and joined the architectural firm of Mayer, Whittlesey and Glass as an architectural designer. In 1958 he became associate partner of Mayer, Whittlesey and Glass. In 1960 William J. Conklin became partner of the architecture firm under the new name of Whittlesey and Conklin. He continued at the same architectural firm, renamed Conklin and Rossant in 1967.
Reston, Virginia was founded by Robert E. Simon with the intention of creating a Planned Community or New Town in the Northern Virginia area. In order to design a town that reflected Simon's specific goals, he hired the architectural firm Whittlesey and Conklin, which became the primary architects of Reston. In 1962, Whittlesey and Conklin created a master plan for the development. It called for seven Village Centers to be connected by high density residential "sinews," or concentrations of housing units. The Village Centers, themselves, were designed to comprise mixed-use space, incorporating public and private areas into a single Village Center. For example, in the first Village Center at Lake Anne, apartments and townhouses were built adjacent to shops and public recreation spaces.
By 1963 construction had begun on the first Village Center, Lake Anne. Surrounding Lake Anne are several different building designs. A large pedestrian walking area, a sculptured fountain, and shops were built in this space. Apartments were built above the shops. Once again, this arrangement reflects the mixed-use intentions of the architects.The architects tried to anticipate all the needs of persons using the Lake Anne Village Center. For example, they designed sculptures that were also used by children for recreation.
Scope and Content
The Conklin and Rossant Reston project collection is divided into six series with four subseries. The collection includes items that relate to the construction and planning of Reston by Conklin and Rossant Architects. The collection begins with the initial plans done by Rossant before he and Conklin formed their architectural firm in 1967. The documents include plans, reports, correspondence and brochures about Reston. Also included are photographs, drawings and negatives which were used in the construction of Reston.
Series 1 is entitled Job Files which is dated from 1960 to 1989 and is divided into four subseries by job number. Subseries 1.1 is Job no. 153 which is information on the First Village Center. Subseries 1.2 is Job no. 123 with correspondence, reports, zoning and publicity. Subseries 1.3 is Job no. 189 about the Reston Town Center. Subseries 4 is comprised of three jobs, 250, 165 and 216 which includes correspondence, reports and publicity relating to the different jobs.
Series 2 is comprised of plans, reports and correspondence. The series is dated from 1960 to 1987. Included in the series are information on the Master Plan for Reston, different building projects, Reston Low Income Housing Demonstration Program Report and other general information about the construction in Reston.
Series 3 is entitled publicity and is dated from 1960-1987. The information in this series is a variety of different publicity material from Reston. Some of the documents are news clippings about the innovations in Reston. Publicity was sent nationally as well as internationally and included is a booklet about Reston written in Japanese.
Series 4 is comprised of a variety of brochures and is dated from 1960 to 1975. The brochures in this collection are mostly for utilities such as windows, fireplaces and furniture. The information was used during the construction and decorating period of the new buildings in Reston.
Series 5 are images dated from 1960-1990. The images are photographs and slides taken around Reston. The images are from during construction and the completion of the construction for publicity purposes.
Series 6 is the oversize series which is dated from 1960-1967. The series is mostly drawing negatives of Reston. The negatives are sketches for different building designs and photographs of the finished buildings. The last item in the series is a book of the drawings and photographs by Conklin and Rossant.
Arrangement
Organized into six series.
Series 1: Job Files, 1960-1989 (Boxes 1-15)
Series 2: Plans, Reports and Correspondence, 1960-1987 (Boxes 15-20)
Series 3: Publicity, 1960-1987 (Boxes 20-22)
Series 4: Brochures, 1960-1975 (Boxes 22-23)
Series 5: Images, 1960-1990 (Boxes 24-25)
Series 6: Oversize, 1960-1967 (Box 26)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
The Special Collections and Archives also holds the Planned Community Archives and other personal papers and organizational records that document Reston, Virginia, and other planned communities.
Index Terms
Geographical Names:
Reston (Va.)
Subjects:
Housing--Virginia--Reston.
Contents List
- Series 1: Job Files, 1960-1989
  Series one is entitled Job Files which is dated from 1960 to 1989 and is divided into four subseries by job number. The information includes First Village Center, correspondence, reports and plans relating to the job.
  - Subseries 1.1: Job no. 153, 1960-1970
    Subseries 1 is Job no. 153 which is information on the First Village Center.
    - First Village File List (Reston Architectural), 1960s (Box 1, Folder 1)
      212.1
    - First Village Center Proposal, Suggested Forms of Contact and Correspondence, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      212.2
    - First Village Center Contracts, Signed and billing, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      212.3
    - First Village Center Contracts, Signed and Billing, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      212.4
    - First Village Center Correspondence with Client, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      212.5
    - First Village Center Correspondence with Client, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      212.6
    - First Village Center Correspondence with Client, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      213.1
    - First Village Center Correspondence with Client, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      213.2
    - First Village Center Correspondence with Client, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      213.3
    - First Village Center Correspondence with Client, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      213.4
    - First Village Center Correspondence with McKinley, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      213.5
    - First Village Center Correspondence with McKinley, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      213.6
    - First Village Center Correspondence with McKinley, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      214.1
    - First Village Center Correspondence with McKinley, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      214.2
    - First Village Center Construction Division (Rowland, Meagher, Bagnato), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      214.3
    - First Village Center Construction Division (Rowland, Meagher, Bagnato), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      214.4
    - First Village Center Commercial (James B. Selonick), 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      214.5
    - First Village Center Commercial (James B. Selonick), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      214.6
    - First Village Center Commercial (James B. Selonick), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      215.1
    - First Village Center Commercial (James B. Selonick), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      215.2
    - First Village Center Commercial (James B. Selonick), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      215.3
    - First Village Center Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      215.4
    - First Village Center Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      215.5
    - First Village Center Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      215.6
    - First Village Center Construction Costs, Rents, Sales Prices, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      215.7
    - First Village Center J.K. Meager, Estimating Costs, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      215.8
    - First Village Center Plaza Fountain (Mermaid Fountain and Others), 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      215.9
    - First Village Center Eastern Architectural Models (Found Empty 1991), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      216.1
    - First Village Center Photographers: Checkman Bossard Maris, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      216.2
    - First Village Center William A. Brown, Consulting Engineer, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      216.3
    - First Village Center Herman Blum, Consulting Engineer, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      216.4
    - First Village Center Herman Blum, Consulting Engineer, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      216.5
    - First Village Center Herman Blum, Consulting Engineer, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      216.6
    - First Village Center Herman Blum Consulting Engineer, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      216.7
    - First Village Center Herman Blum, Consulting Engineer, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      216.8
    - First Village Center Herman Blum, Consulting Engineer, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      216.9
    - First Village Center Herman Blum, Consulting Engineer, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      217.1
    - First Village Center Herman Blum Consulting Engineer, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      217.2
    - First Village Center Severud, Elstad, Krueger Associates, Consulting Engineers, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      217.3
    - First Village Center Severud, Elstad, Krueger Associates, Consulting Engineer, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      217.4
    - First Village Center Severud Associates, Consulting Engineer, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      217.5
    - First Village Center Severud Associates, Consulting Engineer, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      217.6
    - First Village Center Dan Kiley, Landscape Architect, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      218.1
    - First Village Center Meade Palmer, Landscape Architect, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      218.2
    - First Village Center Minutes of Meetings, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      218.3
    - First Village Center Job Meeting with Contractor, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      218.4
    - First Village Center Justin Henshell, Specification Writer, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      218.5
    - First Village Center Outline Specifications, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      218.6
    - First Village Center Outline Specifications, Federal Housing Administration, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      218.7
    - First Village Center Reston, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      226.23
  - Subseries 1.2: Job no. 123, 1961-1972
    Subseries 2 is Job no. 123 with correspondence, reports, zoning and publicity.
    - Reston (Virginia) Legal, Hayes, Sklary and Herzberg (Including Restrictive Covenant), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      219.12
    - Reston (Virginia) Correspondence with Owner, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      220.1
    - Reston (Virginia) Correspondence with Owner, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      220.2
    - Reston (Virginia) Correspondence with Owner, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      220.3
    - Reston (Virginia) Correspondence with Owner, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      220.4
    - Reston (Virginia) Correspondence with Owner, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      220.5
    - Reston (Virginia) The code of the County of Fairfax, Amendment and Subdivision Amendment, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Reston (Virginia) Zoning Amendment (Copies), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      221.1
    - Reston (Virginia) Eugene Simpson and Brother, Incorporated, 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      221.2
    - Reston (Virginia) Eugene Simpson and Brother, Incorporated, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      221.3
    - Reston (Virginia) Zoning Documents and Correspondence with Bauknight, Prichard, McCaudlish and Williams, 1962 and 1965 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      221.4
    - Reston (Virginia) Bauknight, Prichard, McCaudlish and Williams (legal regarding Eugene Simpson), 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      221.5
    - Reston Publicity, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      229.1
    - Reston Publicity, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      229.2
    - Reston Publicity, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      229.3
    - Roads and Mass Transit, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      229.4
    - Eberlin and Eberlin, Engineers, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      229.5
    - Reston Correspondence with Peter McCandless and Norwitch (Advertisement and Public Relations), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      229.7
    - Reston, Public Relations, Weingarten Ricards Dawson, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      229.8
    - Reston, Seynour Evans Associates Incorporated, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      229.9
    - Reston (Virginia) Correspondence with Owner, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      229.10
    - Reston (Virginia) Correspondence with Owner, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      229.11
    - Reston (Virginia) Architects for Industrial Rouse, Dubin and Ventura, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      230.1
    - Reston (Virginia) Architectural Review Board, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      230.2
      - To Robert E. Simon; from Anthony P. Devito; Subuects discussed at the December 2nd meeting of the Architectural Review Board, 3 December 1965; 1.
      - Memorandum; To: Architectural Review Board, From: Carol R. Lubin; Re: Guide Lines, April 24, 1964; 2.
    - Reston (Virginia) Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      230.3
    - Reston (Virginia) Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      230.4
    - Reston (Virginia) Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      230.5
    - Reston (Virginia) House Design Approvals, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      230.6
    - Reston (Virginia) Blank Forms for Reston Architectural Design Control Committee, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 8)
      230.7
    - Reston (Virginia) Lot Sales Weekly Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      230.8
    - Reston (Virginia) Lighting Consultants, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      230.9
    - Reston (Virginia) Development Costs, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      230.10
    - Reston (Virginia) Information on Utility, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      230.11
    - Reston (Virginia) Background Material, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 13)
      230.12
    - Reston (Virginia) Demographic Studies, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      231.18
    - Reston (Virginia) James M. Riche Associates (Industrial), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      231.2
    - Reston (Virginia) H.R.H. Construction Corporation (Contractors), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Reston (Virginia) Engineering, Massey Engineers, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Reston (Virginia) Hospital Site, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      231.5
    - Reston (Virginia) University of Pennsylvania, Davis A. Wallace (Professor of City Plan), 1962 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      231.6
    - Reston (Virginia) Transportation, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      231.7
    - Reston (Virginia) Keyes, Lethbrige and Condon (Architects), 1964 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      231.8
    - Reston (Virginia) Conference Center and Hotel at Reston (Design Problem at Pratt), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      231.9
    - Reston (Virginia) Phase I, Field Visit Reports, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      231.10
    - Reston (Virginia) Boat Design Competition through Pratt, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      231.11
    - Reston (Virginia) Reston Exhibit at Pratt Institute and Architectural League and Washington University, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      231.12
    - Reston (Virginia) Demographic Studies, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Reston (Virginia) Playground Corporation of America, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      231.14
    - Reston (Virginia) Garden Apartments, High Density Sinew, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      231.15
    - Reston (Virginia) Minutes from Meetings and Agendas for Meetings, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      231.16
    - Reston (Virginia) Minutes of Meetings and Agendas for Meetings, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      231.17
    - Reston (Virginia) Robert P. Gersin Associates Industrial Design, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      233.1
    - Reston (Virginia) Data and Notes, Planning Concepts, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      233.2
    - Reston (Virginia) 30 Acre Facility (Government Department), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      233.3
    - Reston (Virginia) Home Association Study, Urban Land Institute with Memo from Livingston Goddard, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      233.4
    - Reston (Virginia) Chloethical Woodard Smith and Associates, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      233.5
    - Reston (Virginia) Models, Paul Crocker and Others, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      233.6
    - Reston (Virginia) Chermayeff and Geismar Associates (Graphics), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      233.7
    - Reston (Virginia) Slide List Used with Reston Lectures, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      233.8
    - Reston (Virginia) Edmund B. Ault, Golf Course, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      233.11
    - Reston (Virginia) Charles M. Goodman Associates (Architect), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      233.12
    - Reston (Virginia) Resume of Robert E. Simon, Jr., 1960s (Box 12, Folder 11)
      233.13
    - Reston (Virginia) Robert Geddes (Architect), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      233.14
    - Reston (Virginia) Eugene H. Klaber Correspondence, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      233.16
    - Reston (Virginia) Weekly Status Reports, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      233.17
    - Reston (Virginia) Churches (Protestant and Catholic), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      233.18
    - Reston (Virginia) Sculpture, Gonzale Fonseca Banner, Laliberte, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      233.19
    - Reston Village No. 7 Area (Hunter's Wood), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      233.20
    - Reston (Virginia) High Rise Feasibility Study (Cohen and Haft), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      233.21
    - Reston (Virginia) Town Center Research, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      233.23
    - Reston (Virginia) Springfield Surveys, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      232.1
    - Reston (Virginia) Severud, Elstad, Kruger Associates, Consulting Structural Engineers, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      232.2
    - Reston, Arthur D. Little, Incorporated (Planning Memoranda on Reston), 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      232.3
    - Reston, "Reston Times" (newspaper) Ralf Segman, Editor, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      232.4
    - Reston, Proposal-Contract-Billing, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      232.5
    - Reston, Proposal-Contract-Billing, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      232.6
    - Reston, Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      232.7
    - Reston, National Capital Planning Community, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      232.8
    - Reston, Report: Fairfax County Economic and Industrial Development Committee, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      232.9
    - Reston, Project Reports (Monthly), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      232.10
    - Reston, Harland, Bartholomew and Associates (previous Planners for Reston), 1964 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      233.15
    - Reston, Roster of Persons Connect with the Job no. 123, including addresses and telephone numbers, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      234.2
    - Reston, Change Orders, Phase 1, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      234.3
    - Reston, Bulletins, Phase 1, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      234.4
    - Reston, Requisitions, Phase 1, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      234.5
    - Reston, Construction, Phase 1 (Correspondence), 1963 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      234.6
    - Reston, Record of Lectures, Talks and Slide Presentations on Reston, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      234.7
    - Reston, President's Task Force, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      234.8
    - Reston, Schools (Candill, Rowlett, Scott), 1964 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      234.9
      - Summary of School Enrollment Estimates and Required Schools, 3 August 1962; 1.
    - Reston, Draft Article by Zukowski, Public Relations, writer, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      234.10
    - Reston, Dan Kiley, Landscape Architect, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      234.12
    - Reston, Zoning, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      227.7
    - Reston, Job 123 Reading Copy and Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      226.24
    - Reston, Eugene Simpson and Brother, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      222.1
    - Reston, Simpson/Reston Matter (Legal Questions), 1967-1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      222.2
  - Subseries 1.3: Job no. 189, 1964-1989
    Subseries 3 is Job no. 189 about the Reston Town Center.
    - Town Center, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      219.5
    - Reston Town Center, Cartsky and Associates, Correspondence and Report, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      219.7
    - Reston Town Center, Billing and Project Report for Town Center, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      219.8
    - Reston Town Center, Minutes of Meetings, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      219.9
    - Reston Town Center, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      219.11
    - Reston Town Center, Reston Planning Committee, Zoning, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      219.10
  - Subseries 1.4: Job no. 250, 165 and 216, 1965-1968
    Subseries 4 is comprised of three jobs, 250, 165 and 216 which includes correspondence, reports and publicity.
    - Low Income Housing, Work Reports, no. 250, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      222.3
    - Low Income Housing, Distribution of Reports, no. 250, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      222.4
    - Low Income Housing, Study Grant, Publicity, Photos, and Loan Reports, no. 250, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Low Income Housing, The Industrialized System for Construction of Flats (Neaux, France: Michel Villaneau), no. 250, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      222.6
    - Low Income Housing, Research Study Grant, no. 250, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      222.7
    - Low Income Housing, Formal Application for Grant to Housing and Urban Development (HUD) and Approval, Budget and Billing, no. 250, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      234.1
    - International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), no. 165, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      231.1
    - Reston Village, Correspondence (Golf Course Island) no. 216, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      219.6
- Series 2: Plans, Reports and Correspondence, 1960-1987
  Series two is comprised of plans, reports and correspondence. The series is dated from 1960 to 1987. Included in the series are Master Plan for Reston and other general information about the construction in the community.
  - Original Reston Town Center Proposal, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    227.3
  - Building "M" and Garden Center, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    227.5
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated, Investment Properties, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 6)
    234.15
  - Notebook of Reston Plan, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 7)